What am I doing here?
Hey...
Didn't you graduate from college?
Well, I don't know if you could
call it college,
it was filled with more
jocks than brains.
Totally weak.
I'll bet.
But if you entered college,
you must have had
something beside window
washing in mind.
So what kind of work did
you really want to do?
Well, actually I wanted
to be a teacher.
A teacher?
You?!
Yeah, right!
What are you doing here,
Masajima?
Aren't you working?
There was a suicide attempt
around here.
Seems like it was some
instructor.
Teachers really do have it tough,
don't they?
Man, if you've got time
to blab about that,
you should be at
the scene of a crime.
You sure you want to talk
to me of like that?
You see, it looks like
this school is taking
applications for teachers.
It seems that a position
suddenly opened.
They're a private school, so even
if you haven't taken the exam,
you could become a teacher.
But it looks like today's
the last day of interviews.
Outta my way!
I can do it!
I can!
I can become a teacher!
Onizuka-san, why do you wish
to work at this school?
Um, well, you see...
I want to be a teacher.
What is there about yourself
that qualifies you to be a teacher?
Well, my physical strength.
You see, I was a master at karate
in the college club,
I figure that would come in handy.
What are you talking about.
This kind of person probably thinks
that if he becomes a teacher,
he can become friendly
with high school girls.
It must be, sir.
What has become
of the schools nowadays.
To think that such unintelligent
and uncultured people come
to interviews now.
Isn't it so pathetic.
That's enough, you can go.
Talking to someone like
this is a waste of time.
Thanks for coming.
Doesn't he understand Japanese?
We told you to go on home.
What?
What's with that look?
Don't try to intimidate us.
Listen,
this isn't a place for trash to come,
trash like you!
Excuse me.
- Hi lady, one milk!
- Coming right up.
How much?
Let's see, milk is 80 yen.
Okay, here's 100.
Here you go, 20 yen change.
What's wrong, the interview
was not good?
You can tell?
They said this isn't a place
for trash like me.
That's not true.
Oh, no need to console me.
I've given up on this place already.
But you know lady,
why are all teachers like that?
As soon as they see my face,
they assume I'm stupid
and I'm trash?
If I were a teacher,
I'd never do that,
thinking of my students as trash.
Hey, Head Teacher, where
are you! Come out!
We're gonna kill you!
Why don't you go stop them.
They might decide to hire you.
Come on out, you bastard!
It's those student we expelled!
Come back here!
Hold it!
- Who the hell are you!
- A teacher.
Someone who would respect
the head teacher.
Onizuka-kun!
If you get rid of these two,
we'll reconsider hiring you!
No no, I'm not doing this for that.
You should just give
it up and go on home.
He won't listen to us at all!
Shut up, you little trash!
Onizuka-kun, do you know
what they did?
In this respectable school!
So you're going to expel us for that?
- We apologized!
- Who's going to believe you?
Trash like you,
as soon as it's over,
you'll be up to your
delinquency again!
Onizuka-kun, hurry
and do something.
You can go ahead
and rough them up.
If they're left to live, they'll just
cause more problems, this trash!
What? What's wrong?
Sir! Sir!
Don't be so damn condescending
with your "trash"!
Can't you forgive them
for what they did?
It's because of teachers like you
that kids like them
end up with nowhere to go!
If that's what you're looking for,
then I'll decline this teaching
position, idiots!
SORIMACHI TAKASHI
MATSUSHIMA NANAKO
KONDÔ YOSHIMASA
ENJÔJI AYA
KOBAYASHI MASAHIRO
IDA KUNIHIKO
KIRARI
IKEUCHI HIROYUKI
YAMAZAKI YÛTA
TOKUYAMA HIDENORI
KUBOZUKA YÔSUKE
NAKAMURA AIMI
KURODA MIKI
OGURI SHUN
FUJIKI NAOHITO
MABUCHI ERIKA
TATEISHI RYÔKO
SHIMOTSUKA MAKOTO
ANEZAKI KUMI
GUADALCANAL TAKA
KIKUCHI KIN'YA
NAKAO AKIRA
SHIRAKAWA YUMI
English Subtitles by
STUDIO NEW MEDIA
Subtitles Edited and Timed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
AKABANE HIROSHI
A Production of
KANSAI TEREBI & AVEC
Excuse me...
Hey bro, how about it,
would you lend us some cash?
Our families are poor
and we don't have any money.
What's up with him?
We're gonna kill you!
Now then, here's the question,
who's going to get killed first,
One, the karate expert who's
in a bad mood from something
that just happened to him.
Or two, the two idiots trying
to get money from that guy...
You shouldn't have, using
your allowance to buy me
a weeks worth of stuff.
Geeze! Don't you know, minors
shouldn't be smoking these!
Gimme a light.
Study hard now.
Damn...
Just what the heck am I doing...
Oh man! Haven't I told you
you shouldn't
just barge into someone's place?
Geeze, you should clean up some!
This place ain't fit for a human!
This isn't your place, go home!
Oh, I see, I see, your interview
was no good after all.
Gee, too bad.
You sound almost happy 'bout that!
Well, the idea of you becoming
a teacher is impossible.
You becoming an officer
is even more impossible!
Give up on being a teacher.
You should become a cop,
you can beat up two or three
- yakuza and no one'll complain.
- Man, you're the worst!
Someone came by a while ago.
The director of the Musashino
Seirin Academy,
Sakurai Akira.
She said if you're still interested
in becoming a teacher,
to come by the end of the day.
Dammit! Why didn't you
tell me earlier!
This time I can really
become a teacher!
If they find out about this,
I'm going to have to write up
a report you know!
You're too slow.
Come on, step on it!
Hey stupid! Cut it out!
Director, are you here?
It's me, Onizuka.
Onizuka Eikichi.
Director?
Guess I didn't make it in time...
I've been waiting,
Onizuka-kun.
I'm Akira Sakurai,
the director of this school.
What is it?
That time...
Oh that. You see,
it's a little hobby of mine.
Well, I looked into you.
So, it's amazing there's someone
with a history like this!
Looks like you've given
the police a hard time!
Okay,
you're hired.
You start tomorrow.
This is the school outline,
and the teacher's manual.
Read them by tomorrow.
What's wrong?
Yes, well, I still can't believe it.
I was wishing for a teacher
like you.
You see, this school is viewed
as a traditional academy.
But in reality it's filled
with problems.
And it's not just the students,
there's all kinds of teachers.
For that reason,
it'll take great strength to fix.
You're the only one left
who can do it.
Please help us, Onizuka-kun.
No...
Onizuka-sensei.
Ex-Excuse me...
Could you say that again?
Onizuka-sensei.
You can count on me,
Director!
Hold on a minute.
However, there is one condition.
- What is it?
- Will you listen?
Oh, I don't want to go
to school already.
Good morning!
I'm Onizuka Eikichi,
I will be your homeroom
teacher from today.
Maybe I should just be normal.
Yo, I'm Onizuka.
Maybe that's a little too much.
That's right...
I gotta phone mom!
My dear mother,
from today, your son
has become a teacher.
In all the excitement yesterday,
I was unable to inform you.
Oh gee, what now.
Hello, this is Fuyutsuki.
Oh, hello!
Today?
I'm sorry, I can't today.
Yes, please call again.
Thanks.
What a pest!
I'm not going to keep this one.
Oh well, might as well go.
Business time!
Perfect!
Good morning!
Morning!
Um, excuse me.
You're a teacher from Musashino
Seirin Academy, right?
Yes, that's right.
I'm starting today,
Onizuka Eikichi.
Excuse me, but could
I ask your name?
I'm sorry, but I'm in a rush.
When I thought about
when I cross this,
I'll be teacher,
I got kinda nervous.
Just what are you thinking?
Hiring trash like that!
Listen,
having a person like him around,
I think it'll liven up this academy.
Yes, but if he causes trouble,
no I'm sure he will...
I must object!
After the previous principle quit,
do you know why I left
the position open?
Do you understand?
Rather than select someone new,
I thought it would be better to leave
it for someone from this school.
I see, Director!
If Onizuka-kun causes
any problems,
we have an agreement
that he will resign.
In addition...
Additionally?
Yes...
I'm assigning him,
second year, class four.
Second year, class four?
Yes.
Director, you're quite devious,
aren't you.
Do you think so?
Man, I'm nervous!
Good morning, teacher!
I'm a teacher...
Good morning!
Oh, Fuyutsuki-sensei.
Could you be on staff
this summer?
Kotani-sensei can't make it.
What?
I can't! I already promised
my friend we'd go on a trip.
Well then, can you two
discuss it?
Here you go.
Um, Kotani-sensei...
I'm sorry, but I can't.
I'm sorry, but could you
somehow?
It's impossible.
Do you think an old lady like me
might have nothing else to do?
I didn't...
Don't be so harsh, Kotani-sensei,
Fuyutsuki-sensei is asking first.
Well Hakamada-sensei,
that's because
you're a fan on Fuyutsuki-sensei.
That has nothing to do with this!
Don't worry about it,
I'll figure something out.
Then I'll leave it up
to Kotani-sensei.
- Fuyutsuki-sensei.
- Yes?
Could you photocopy this?
Yes.
Idiot...
But you know, during summer
vacation, the students and
staff should be dismissed.
What are you going to do
this summer?
I'll be running physical activities,
so I'll be on campus.
You're so into it, aren't you?
It's too hot!
What about you,
Teshigawara-sensei?
During cram school season,
I stay inside and work on my PC.
It's too hot to go outside.
That's no good! Lack of exercise is
the worst for you!
You're not looking to well either.
You should join me at the gym,
when are you free?
To associate even on
private time...
Well, what about working at
a cram school on private time?
My only purpose is to get even one
more student into a good college.
That again.
That's what the students
and parents want the most.
To fulfill that is the duty
of teachers, right?
Right, Fuyutsuki-sensei?
Well, yes...
It looks like Teshigawara-sensei
likes Fuyutsuki-sensei, too.
I bumped into him
just a while ago,
is there a new teacher
starting today?
Yes, there is.
The director hired him.
Then he must be a genius.
What University is he from?
He's not. He's from some
third rate college
and took seven years
to graduate.
On top of that, he used
to be in a bike gang.
Even though we turned
him down.
What's the head teacher say?
Well, he just sucks up
to the director.
When it comes to a critical
moment, he's useless.
If it were me, I'd tell her off!
Oh, but you never say anything when
the head teacher is around.
Excuse me...
What's this teacher's name?
Excuse me.
I'm Onizuka Eikichi.
I will be working with you
from today.
I will be counting on your
assistance, pleased to meet you.
Um...
Excuse me...
Thanks for earlier!
Good morning, Head Teacher.
I'll tell you this,
I do not consider you a teacher.
This is your homeroom class.
Second year, class four?
That's right, second year,
class four.
Is there something
about class 2-4?
Fuyutsuki-sensei.
Excuse me,
could you show him his class?
Yes.
The smell of school is really
is great, isn't it?
When I was in elementary school,
we had a kind and beautiful
Madonna
of a teacher like you.
She was the favorite of everyone.
This is going to be the best!
Alright!
I wouldn't be so happy,
if I were you.
What?
Class 2-4 has always been filled
with all of the trouble students.
The previous homeroom teacher
had a nervous breakdown,
and the one before that disappeared
and is still missing.
Oh, don't worry about it.
Anyway, they're all the ones
no one cares about, right?
I'm used to that.
Oh, thanks.
I'm your homeroom teacher
from today, Eikichi Onizuka.
Any complaints?
- This is class 2-4, right?
- Yes!
Teacher,
are you done with your
introduction?
Yeah.
We want to know more about you.
He looks pretty nice.
He's your type, isn't he,
Nanako?
Cut it out!
You're in this class?
Teacher, they really are sorry
about what they did.
- We're very sorry.
- We'll never do that again.
As long as you understand,
that's fine.
I don't have any hard feelings.
What's this, you're all
good kids!
Alright, let's all work together!
Yes!
Let's all make this
a great school together!
Yes!
You guys are perfect!
Okay, let's take roll.
When your name is called,
please stand.
- Aizawa Miyabi.
- Here.
- Akiyama Tadanobu.
ONIZUKA, KILL...
- Iijima Kyôko.
- Here.
- Izumi Shôko.
- Ichikawa Ryûta.
- Here.
- Ero Kyôko.
- Kamioka Ken.
- Here.
- Kawamura Kimitoshi.
- Kikuchi Yoshito.
- Here.
Are you the class leader?
Nice to meet you.
Same here.
- Let's see, Kitahara Sanae.
- Here.
Kisano Tadae.
IQ: I IMAGINE NOT MUCH
No, I'm a teacher.
Do you have Kinpachi-sensei?
I said, Kinpachi-sensei.
Nanako, what's wrong?
Help me, teacher.
Can you wait a sec,
it's a mess.
CONGRATULATION
FOR YOUR FIRST EXPERIENCE
So... what's wrong?
Tell me.
I... don't want to go home.
Why?
Did you have a fight
with your dad?
C'mon, you can be honest
with me, I'll listen to you.
Nanako, what are you doing!
Are you hot?
I'll turn on the A/C.
Oh, I don't have A/C...
You know when you open
the fridge, it get's a little cooler...
Hold on, Nanako!
W-Wait!
- Teacher...
- Nanako...
Sorry about this.
Okay!
Okay Nanako! Check it out!
Alright!
What a scoop!
I can see the headlines,
"Pervert Teacher!"
You've done it now, teacher!
How terrible, with a student!
Nanako, that was
something else!
But what was he thinking?
Was he thinking it was okay?
What a dirty teacher! Stupid!
Bring us 1,000,000 yen
in a week.
2-4 is going to live it up
this summer!
Otherwise we're gonna put
this all over the school.
Or maybe we'll sell it to a paper.
C'mon, let's go,
remember, 1,000,000.
Hey, check it out, he's got
all of Kinpachi!
We're goin' now.
- Idiot!
- Nanako,
is this what you were planning
from the start?
Were you lying about
having a problem?
Even if I did, why would
I come to you, a teacher!
What a joke, that Onizuka.
He's nothing.
That's how teachers are.
They're so easy.
Hey, Nanako, think
of something else.
Yeah, if it's this easy to get 1,000,000,
then we can do anything.
I'm going.
- What? Hey, wait!
- Nanako!
- Wait, Nanako!
Thanks for earlier.
Who the hell are you?
Hey you! Do you know
who this is?
We're the Kanagawa 2,000,
he's the Onizuka Eikichi that
single-handedly united us all!
This is dirty, Onizuka!
Calling out your hoods like this!
- So what of it?
- You can't resort to violence!
If you lay a finger on us, we'll report
you to the teachers' board!
You'll be put away!
We'll go to the papers, you pervert
teacher. Do you want that?
You'll never be a teacher!
- Do whatever you want.
- What?
But first...
I'll kill you.
How about it?
You talk big.
Don't think all adults are going
to do exactly as you say!
Jacuzzi...
What a wonderful sound.
Now I can melt away all the troubles
from the school office.
Wait dad! I'm going first!
But Yoshiko, the Jacuzzi
just came today, so I...
I hate going after you dad,
it's so dirty!
- Mama, dinner.
- Huh?
Weren't you going to take
a bath?
Yoshiko went first.
Hurry it up, will you?
I can't do it so suddenly.
Besides, I can't stop now.
You know, you may always
treat me like a fool,
But today the director discussed
the principle's position with me...
The phone!
Answer it! You're not
doing anything anyway.
Hello, Uchiyamada residence.
It's Nakamaru, it's terrible, sir!
Did I hear that right?
Just what kind of a teacher calls
his gang friends and drags his
students all around town?
Don't you have any
common sense!
I'm sorry. If I don't teach them
a lesson, I'll lose respect.
What's that?
Is that any way for a teacher
to talk?
If news of this got out,
what do you think would happen?
I'm sure it'll be all over
the place!
It's just that they were
playing dirty.
Never mind already!
It's a waste of time
talking to you.
We'll get the facts ourselves.
- Get out of here!
- Just don't fire me.
You're not going to be fired.
You're going to quit.
Don't you understand
what I'm saying?
Right, Director?
Oh, excuse me,
you know when you get older...
Director!
Uchiyamada-sensei,
isn't there some other way?
That man hurt our students!
Looks like it can't be helped,
Onizuka-kun.
You see this,
this was a condition
for hiring him,
that he would always have
this with him.
If he ever caused any problems,
he would quit immediately.
That's brilliant, Director.
Oh, you two, there's no need
to worry.
This man will soon be leaving.
So, could you please keep
this to yourselves?
It'll become such a bother
if the teachers' board
found out about this.
Please don't quit,
Onizuka-sensei!
We were wrong.
What do you mean?!
From now on we will follow
our teacher.
We ask for his guidance
in our lives.
I see, I see.
I knew you two would
understand.
Let's work together
from now on.
Geeze!
You needed to do exactly
as we agreed!
A little later, and I would have
really been fired!
You know, you guys botched up
your lines, it's amazing it worked.
- So what do you say?
- Yes, sir.
You better go study.
Go on!
You!
You're despicable!
Hi Onitchi!
Shee, whatcha want?
Why so cold? And I was going
to compliment you.
- Compliment?
- Yup.
All the teachers up to now
would either pay the money or
do whatever we told them.
Onitchi, you're something else!
Stop pestering me,
I ain't gonna hang
out with some kid in wet
diapers like you.
Teacher, do you want
to come over to my house?
Why would I want to?
They're not coming home
tonight, my parents.
MIZUKI
Holy cow! Your house
is unreal!
Check out how high
the ceiling is!
So, just what do your
parents do?
Papa is the manager for a franchise
of Japanese restaurants.
Mama owns a dry goods store
and the four adjacent stores.
It seems like they're both so busy
they don't even have time to
see their daughters face.
Is this your dinner?
No way!
Yeah, terrible, isn't it?
It's always like this. Last time
they just left money
and told me to get whatever
I wanted.
Isn't this premium sushi?
You know, I've seen stuff
like this,
but I've never eaten it before.
Hey!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Oh man, my ôtoro...
Look, the uni,
the uni is crying!
So Azusa-san is a high
school teacher.
So does that mean we're going
to be graded today?
That's right. No one's gotten
a perfect score yet.
Stop that!
Um...
What type of men
do you like?
Well... there aren't really
any types I don't like.
So if you find someone good,
you'll marry him?
Yes, of course.
So, teacher...
Excuse me,
but could you not call
me teacher?
You have to excuse her.
Azusa doesn't like to be
called "teacher".
Azusa actually wanted to be
a stewardess, but there was
a shortage of positions.
But you haven't given up
on it, right?
She has her resignation ready,
so she can quit any time.
No way!
So, what do you think
of the one in the middle?
No way, him?
Azusa, your ideals
are too high.
That guy from the export
company was good too.
Why didn't you keep
that one?
He had too much of an ego.
You know, you only have
one chance at life.
When I find someone,
I want to feel, "this is the guy!"
It's because of that that your
chances keep slipping away.
Your only boyfriend's been
the one from college, right?
How old do you think you are,
Fuyutsuki-sensei?
Here, "aaahhh"!
Cut it out, people
are watching!
Hey Onitchi, how come you
only ordered rice?
Um well... Japanese food
is rice, right?
Don't worry about money.
That's a platinum card, wow!
Is that what color they are?
I've never seen one before.
Hold on, menu please.
I'll have the C course.
It's none of my business...
Will you let me stay at
your place today?
What?
It's not like that!
This time's not a trap!
You know, do you know
what it means for
a woman to go over
to a man's place?
Of course.
Isn't there some way?
Has Onizuka caused any
other problems?
There's nothing...
Then find something!
Excuse me, Head Teacher...
What is it?
It's about Onizuka-sensei...
Hello, this is Musashino Seirin
Academy.
This is class 2-4's
Mizuki Nanako's mother.
We're asking you,
where did you stay last night?
Your parents are asking
how the school
will take responsibility for this.
If you don't tell us, we won't be
able to understand.
Speak up!
Where were you?
She was at my place.
What?
Why didn't you tell them?
You had a student from your
class in your room?
Just what were
you thinking?!
She said she didn't want
to go home.
Now we know what you are!
What did you do?!
No, no, I don't want to know!
We know you were up
to no good!
- Sir...
- In any case,
go on home.
I'll discuss this with your
parents.
Until then, don't say
anything, okay?
I'm not going back
to that house.
What are you talking about?!
I'm going to stay
with Onizuka-sensei.
Just a minute!
Nakamaru-sensei, don't stand
there! Hurry!
A high school girl's suddenly
staying with you, huh?
Gee, that's terrible.
Isn't it?
But isn't it great, your
dream's come true.
What?
Didn't you become a teacher so you
could get it on with a "kogal"?
Man, you get all the breaks.
Cop's never get any action
like that, shit.
Hey...
Could it be, you've never
done it before?
That means you're still
a virgin?
No way!
That's too funny!
You call yourself a friend?
- Tie her up.
- What?!
Tie her up, and take pictures.
I'll need proof, you know.
Oh, welcome home!
It'll be ready soon!
Today's sukiyaki.
Onitchi, you like it,
don't you?
Wow, I think it's been ten years
since I've had sukiyaki!
Excuse me...
oh, you cleaned up.
This brings back memories.
A long time ago, Papa's payday
would be sukiyaki day.
Mama and I would cook it a lot.
It was a small place like this.
But I didn't care at all.
Because it was so small,
Papa and Mama would
always be close by.
It was fun then.
When we got rich,
and lived in a big house,
I thought we'd be even happier
than we were then.
In that house now,
between Papa and Mama's room,
there's a wall.
When you touch it...
It's ice cold.
I want to go back.
Back to those times.
Is there a way?
It'd be great to go back
to those times.
Don't you think?
I want to go back.
Go home.
This isn't the apartment
you used to be in.
It isn't like I expected anything
from the beginning anyway!
Not from a teacher!
We told you so.
Onizuka's just some
violent teacher.
Don't worry 'bout him,
we'll take care of him some day.
Hey, Nanako!
Hello, this is Fuyutsuki.
Hello, Fuyutsuki-sensei?
This is Nakamaru.
- Hello, can you hear me?
- Please hold on.
Thanks for waiting,
what is it?
Well, Mizuki Nanako hasn't
returned home yet.
Her parents are furious!
I'm sorry, but could I ask
you to look around for her?
Excuse me, but I'm not
her homeroom teacher.
That homeroom teacher's
missing!
Just what is that man
Onizuka thinking?
I understand, I'll look around.
Excuse me, I was...
For crying out loud!
Why do I have to do
this on my private time?
It's not like I'll find her outside
of the academy anyway!
Teacher.
It's you!
Oh... so you have a secret
side to you, don't you.
Not like at school...
No, I'm meeting a friend...
Teacher...
What do you think of Onitchi?
What?
I guess he's just like any
other guy after all.
That's Fuyutsuki.
Nanako!
Nanako! Where have you been?
What do you think you're doing,
making your parents worry so!
What parents.
What that?
Even though your daughter's gone,
you never realized it until morning!
Nana!
It's because you don't supervise
her that this happens!
Oh! If you would be
more of a father...
What?! Everyday I...
Then please don't give our phone
number to strange women.
How is the school going to take
responsibility for this?
It's because your guidance
is inadequate
that our daughter has
turned out like that.
- Hold on a minute!
- We're very sorry.
You see, this is all because
of an outrageous new teacher,
no, it's embarrassing
to call that man a teacher.
Fuyutsuki-sensei, apologize.
- What? Why?
- Never mind, just do it!
We're very sorry.
You see,
our director isn't familiar
with what actually goes on.
We're in a bind too.
But please don't worry!
I will take responsibility
and properly discipline that man.
- Nanako!
- Onizuka!
What are you doing here!
Go home!
Who... who are you?
I'm a teacher.
Teacher!
Where is it, Nanako?
Stop it!
What are you doing?
We'll call the police!
Onizuka, what...
- The police, call the police!
- Hurry, dear!
No, don't call
the police, wait!
How's that, Nanako?
The rest is up to you.
It was a short time,
but thank you for everything.
It really was short,
wasn't it?
Excuse me.
Onizuka-kun.
Do you have any regrets about
what you did yesterday?
Not at all.
I see.
Are you going to quit?
Please do your best for me too,
I'll be cheering you on
from wherever I am.
This is it, Onizuka!
Director!
That Onizuka can't
escape now!
Do you know what he
did yesterday?
He trespassed and destroyed
property.
That's clearly a crime,
a crime!
One way or another, Director,
this time we must have
that man leave this school!
Hello, this is Musashino Seirin
Academy.
Oh, Mizuki-san!
This is Head Teacher
Uchiyamada.
We're very sorry
about yesterday.
Please don't worry.
That troublemaker teacher,
he will soon be fired.
Onitchi!
You know, it was a mess after
you left yesterday!
Papa and Mama were
furious.
But you know...
After a while, when their eyes met
through that hole in the wall,
they both laughed.
Kinda embarrassingly.
It's been a long time
since I saw that -
their faces like that.
Like when we were
in that little apartment.
I'm all right now.
I don't quite understand it,
but something inside me,
it feels like it's been
lifted and freed.
W-Wait!
If we make Onizuka leave,
you'll cause problems?
What do you mean by that,
Mizuki-san?
Onizuka-kun!
Alright!
Alright! Onitchi,
one point!
Onitchi!
It's my treasure!
Let's use it some day,
okay?
Hey you! When...
Hey Onitchi, let's all use it!
Looks like we can't count
on them.
Man, I'm glad!
I thought I wouldn't be
able to go to class
with you like this,
Fuyutsuki-sensei.
Oh yeah, are you free
tonight?
I haven't god paid yet,
though.
I guess not...
It's okay.
I don't happen to be
doing anything today.
What is it?
It's just that it seems like
the way you're talking changed...
Oh, maybe not then?
No, no, no! Let's go!
But what should we do?
I don't know much about parks
or the beach spots.
I know, I'll go ask
my students.
They may be brats, but they
know about things like that.
You guys, don't you think
this is great?
Right, Fuyutsuki-sensei?
You! You really
are despicable!
2016-03
Press play. Subtitles appear.
200+ languages. One app:  tryray.app